_Last updated: August 29, 2024_

Legination Inc. ("we", "us", or "our") operates [https://www.billtrack50.com](https://www.billtrack50.com/) (the "Website") and BillTrack50 (the "App"). This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of the Website and App.

Information Collection and Use
------------------------------

While using our Website and App, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to, your name, email address, postal address, and phone number ("Personal Information").

We also collect information about your device, including your IP address, browser type, and operating system.

We do not collect or process sensitive information.

**Payment Data.** We may collect data necessary to process your payment if you choose to make purchases, such as your payment instrument number, and the security code associated with your payment instrument. All payment data is handled and stored by Stripe. You may find their privacy notice link(s) here: [https://stripe.com/privacy](https://stripe.com/privacy). We do not store this information ourselves.

**Application Data.** If you use our application(s), we also may collect the following information if you choose to provide us with access or permission:

* ﻿﻿_Mobile Device Data_. We automatically collect device information (such as your mobile device ID, model, and manufacturer), operating system, version information and system configuration information, device and application identification numbers, browser type and version, hardware model Internet service provider and/or mobile carrier, and internet Protocol (IP) address (or proxy server). If you are using our application(s), we may also collect information about the phone network associated with your mobile device, your mobile device's operating system or platform, the type of mobile device you use, your mobile device's unique device ID, and information about the features of our application(s) you accessed.
* ﻿﻿_Push Notifications_. We may request to send you push notifications regarding your account or certain features of the application(s). If you wish to opt out from receiving these types of communications, you may turn them off in your device's settings.

This information is primarily needed to maintain the security and operation of our application(s), for troubleshooting, and for our internal analytics and reporting purposes

Log Data
--------

Like many website and app operators, we collect information that your browser or device sends whenever you visit our Website or use our App ("Log Data"). This Log Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Website that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, and other statistics.

Cookies
-------

Cookies are files with a small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your computer's hard drive.

We use "cookies" to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Website or App.

We use the following types of cookies:

* _Essential cookies_: Necessary for the website to function properly.
* _Analytics cookies_: Help us understand how visitors interact with our website.

We **do not** use third party tracking cookies for advertising purposes.

Use of Data
-----------

We use the collected data for various purposes:

* To provide and maintain our Website and App
* To notify you about changes to our Website and App
* To allow you to participate in interactive features of our Website and App when you choose to do so
* To provide customer support
* To gather analysis or valuable information so that we can improve our Website and App
* To monitor the usage of our Website and App
* To detect, prevent and address technical issues

We may also use your information to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send.

Data Sharing and Disclosure
---------------------------

We may disclose your Personal Information in the following situations:

* To comply with a legal obligation
* To protect and defend our rights or property
* To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Website or App
* To protect the personal safety of users of the Website or App or the public
* To protect against legal liability

We may share your information with third-party service providers to perform services on our behalf, such as payment processing, data analysis, email delivery, hosting services, customer service, newsletters, and onboarding emails.

We do not share or sell your information with any third party for marketing purposes.

Security
--------

The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

Changes to This Privacy Policy
------------------------------

This Privacy Policy is effective as of August 29, 2024 and will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page.

We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Website or App after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.

Your Rights
-----------

Depending on your location, you may have certain rights regarding your personal information, such as:

* The right to access the personal information we hold about you
* The right to request the correction of inaccurate personal information
* The right to request deletion of your personal information
* The right to object to processing of your personal information
* The right to data portability

To exercise any of these rights, please contact us using the information provided below.

**California Privacy Rights:** If you are a California resident, you have the right to request information about the personal information we've collected about you over the past 12 months, and in certain circumstances, you can request that we delete your personal information.

Children's Privacy
------------------

Our Website and App do not address anyone under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with Personal Information, please contact us.

Contact Us
----------

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at:

LegiNation, Inc.

6050 Greenwood Plaza Blvd, Suite 110

Greenwood Village, CO 80111

Email: Info@LegiNation.com
